Privacy
=======

 This is the privacy policy (the ‘**Privacy Policy**’) that defines how we, Frebo App Ltd. (‘**Anybook**,’ ‘**We**, ’‘**Ours**,’ or ‘**Us**’) use the Personal Data (as hereinafter defined)that we collect, receive and store with respect to private persons in connection with the use of: (a) the website _Anybook.ai_ and any website that we operate (hereinafter each, together with its Sub-Domain, content and services, the ‘**Website**’); and (b) the Anybook cellular application (the ‘**Application**’). The Website and the Application, jointly and severally, shall be referred hereinafter: the ‘**Services**.’ In this Privacy Policy words which are in the masculine gender shall be deemed to include the feminine gender, and vice versa.  
  
1.          **Introduction**. This Privacy Policy describes the procedures for the collection of data, the collection and the use of your personal data in connection with the Services. ‘**Persona data**’ means any data that, jointly or severally with other data, might be used for the purpose of personally identifying a person, including, but not limited to, first and last name, personal profile, email, home address or any other physical address, or any other contact information.  
  
2.          **Terms of Use and license agreement for an end user**. This Privacy Policy constitutes part of our Terms of Use that are available in the following link: http://anybook.ai/privacy or in Anybook and that you approved before using the Application(the ‘**Terms**’). Any term not defined in this Privacy Policy shall have the meaning assigned thereto in accordance with these Terms.  
‍  
3.          **Consent and change**. You are not legally obligated to provide us any personal data and you hereby confirm that the provision of your personal data is made out of your own freewill. By using the Services, you agree to the terms set forth in this Privacy Policy and to the collection, processing and sharing of your personal data by us for the purposes as stated hereunder. If you disagree with this Privacy Policy, do not log in or use the Services in any other manner. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change to Privacy Policy at any time. Such a change will enter into force in ten (10) days after the publication of the amended Privacy Policy in the Website/Application and your use of the Services after publication of the Privacy Policy means that you accept these changes.  
‍  
4.          **What personal data do we collect and how do we collect it?** We receive and/or collect from you personal data in the following ways:  
4.1.        Account. In order to use the Services that we offer through the Website and/or the Application, you are required to create an account (the ‘**Account**’). At the time of opening your Account, you will be asked to provide us necessary information for the purpose of providing the Services in an efficient manner, for example information about your location. You may create an Account by clicking the 'connect’ or the ‘login’ option that we may display in the Website or in the Application that are part of the Application or in a designated third-part service (hereinafter each: ‘**Third-Party Account**’) such as Facebook or Google. This action will enable you to link your Account to your Third-Party Account. Should you pursue this option, you will be required to approve such connection, as well as the types of information (that might include personal data)that we will receive from your Third-Party Account and the types of activities that we will perform in connection with your Third-Party Account. Please note that for the purpose of using this option, you will need an existing Third-Party Account to which you might need to connect.  
4.2.         Using the Services. During the time you use the Services, we might collect data about your use of the Services. In addition, after opening the Account, and during the use of the Application, a ‘reader profile’ will be created for you, that will include information about your preferences based on the actions you performed in the Services, such as: favorite genres, favorite authors, favorite categories etc.  
4.3.         ‘Contact.’ If you send us a ‘contact’ request, whether by delivery of an online form that we make available for you, and whether by delivery of an email to the email account we display, you might be required to provide to us specific information, such as your name and email.  
4.4.         Log Files. We may use logfiles. The data contained in the log files includes internet protocol addresses(IP address), browser type, internet services provider (ISP), date/time stamp, reference/exit pages, clicked pages and any other data that your browser might send us. We may use this data for the purpose of analyzing trends, managing the Services, tracking user traffic within the framework of the Services and collecting demographic data.  
4.5.       Cookies and other tracking technologies. Our Services might include the use of “cookies,” anonymous identifiers and other tracking technologies so that we can provide and display to you information that is personally customized to your preferences. A “cookie” file is a small text file that can be used, for example, for the purpose of collecting data about actions in the Services. Certain cookie files and other technologies might be used for the purpose of retrieving personal data, such as an IP address that a user used in the past. Most browsers enable you to control the cookie files, including the option whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. You can select in most of the browsers’ settings whether or not you want to receive such files and how to remove them. You may also select the option in most of the browsers whether or not you are interested in receiving a message that you will receive a cookie file, or whether you wish to block the cookie files by your browser.  
4.6.        Data from mobile devices. We might collect limited data from your mobile device for the purpose of providing and operating the Application. Such data might include the type of your mobile device, the operating system, identifying data of the mobile device and time and date stamps for the purpose of using the Application. In addition, we might use the technology in the Application for the purpose of helping us collecting cumulative statistical data that do not contain personal data.  
4.7.       Google Analytics. The Website might use a tool known by the name of ‘Google Analytics’ for the purpose of collecting data about the use of the Service. Google Analytics collects data such as the frequency users use the Service, the webpages that the users use when visiting the Website and the identity of other websites they used before they reached the Service. We use the data we receive from Google Analytics for the purpose of keeping and improving the Service and our products. We do not integrate the data we collect by the use of Google Analytics with data that enables persona identification. Google’s ability to use and share the data that is collected by Google Analytics about your login to the Service and the use of the Service is as stated in the Google Analytics Terms of Use in the following link: [http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html](http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html), and by the Google privacy policy that is available in the following link: http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/. You may further learn about the manner that Google collects and processes data specifically in connection with Google Analytics in the link: http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/.You can prevent the use of your data by Google Analytics by downloading and installing the browser add-on for the purpose of canceling your approval to the use of Google Analytics, available in the link: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/.  
‍  
5.       **The way we use the personal data**. If you provide the data or in the event we collect personal data by the Services, we might use this personal data in the following ways, in any customary media, including email, text message, mail, fax etc.:    
5.1.       We will use your personal data for the purpose of providing and improving our services, contacting you about the services and the programs or different offers you might have been registered to, and for the purpose of identifying and authenticating your access to the parts of the services you are entitled to access.    
5.2.        In order to send you marketing/advertising materials that we think might interest you (including by email and SMS) and send you updates or news regarding the services and our products, in accordance with the applicable law; you may demand your removal from this distribution list by clicking the proper link in the newsletter that will be sent to you.    
5.3.        For the purpose of processing your requests and responding to queries and complaints.    
5.4.        For the purpose of securing the data in the Website and complying with the provisions of the law.    
5.5.        For the purpose of defending in legal proceedings.  
5.6.        For the purpose of finding, preventing or handling in any other manner any events related to fraud or security issues and for the purpose of protecting from infringement of rights, harm to property or the safety of Anybook, our users or the public.  
‍  
6.        **The manner we share the personal data**  We will not deliver the information that you sent us to third-parties, however only in the following cases, to the extent that this is necessary for the purposes for which we collected the personal data, as stated above:    
1.1.                To service providers that assist us in the regular operation of the Website, the Application and the Services contained therein.    
1.2.                In the event we are obligated to act in such manner in accordance with the law, a judicial order or an instruction from a competent authority.  
1.3.                In the event of legal proceedings that will commence against us in respect of actions that you will perform and with respect to any dispute, argument, claim, demand or legal proceedings, if and to the extent that there are any, between you and us or between you and anyone acting on our behalf.  
  
7.         **Use of anonymous data**. We may use anonymous data (as hereinafter defined) or disclose such data to third-part service providers for the purpose of improving our Services and improving your experience of the Services. We might disclose anonymous data (whether or not in return for consideration) to third-parties, including to advertisers and partners. ‘**Anonymous data**’ means data that does not enable the identification of a single user, such as cumulative statistical data about the use of our Services.    
  
8.           **Unsubscribe**. You may unsubscribe from future emails we send in connection with sales promotions, advertisements or any other emails by selecting the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any email we send you. For your information, even if you cancel your approval to receive the said emails, we might still send you a response to any ‘contact ’request and administrative emails (for example, in connection with a request to create a new password) that are necessary for the purpose of enabling your use of the Services.  
  
9.           **Your rights**. You may request to inspect your personal data. In addition, in the event of data that is inaccurate, you may request to delete and/or amend the personal data. You may submit your requests by sending an email to info@anybook.ai. Your email should include information that is relevant for your request.  
  
10.        **Interaction with and links to third-party products**. The Services might enable you to create an interaction with or contain links to your third-party account and to other third-party websites, mobile software applications and services that we do not own or control (each of the said: ‘**Third-Party Services**’). We are not responsible for the privacy procedures or the content of such Third-Party Service as said. Please note that Third-Party Services might collect personal data from you. Accordingly, we recommend that you read the terms and limitations and the privacy policy of each Third-Party Service that you decide to use or contact with.    
‍  
11.           **Children’s privacy**. The Services are intended for adults who are 18 years of age and older.  
‍  
12.           **Security**. The security of your personal data is important for us. We adhere to customary standards in the industry, including the use of proper administrative, physical and technical means of protection for the purpose of protecting the personal data that was provided to us. Nevertheless, no online data transfer method, or any method for electronic storage, is 100% protected. Therefore, while we aspire to use reasonable and customary measures for the purpose of protecting your personal data, we cannot protect its absolute confidentiality or security. In the event you have questions about service security, you may contact us in the address: [Info@anybook.ai](mailto:Info@anybook.ai).  
   
13.          **Merger, sale or bankruptcy**. In the event we are acquired or merged with a third-party entity, or in the event of bankruptcy or any other similar event, we reserve the right to deliver or to provide personal data with respect to the said events.   
‍  
14.           **Commitment**. We are committed to protecting your privacy. Online protection of your privacy is an evolving sphere of activity and we constantly develop our Service for the purpose of complying with its requirements. In the event you have any comments or questions regarding our privacy policy, or regarding your personal data that we store and use, please contact us in the following address: [Info@anybook.ai](mailto:Info@anybook.ai).    
  
Recently updated: May 2021

**©** All Rights Reserved Frebo App 2021
